<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Suggest on PicoVibe</title><link>/categories/suggest/</link><description>Recent content in Suggest on PicoVibe</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/suggest/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Footage emerges of cop shooting man holding wallet</title><link>/mc2zcuw.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/mc2zcuw.html</guid><description>Dashcam footage from a shocking officer-involved shooting in Alabama has emerged almost three years after the incident.
Airman Michael Davidson was shot by Opelika police officer Phillip Hancock after he responded to a report of erratic driving on Highway 85 the evening of March 6, 2014.
The video shows that as Davidson struggled to get out of his vehicle the officer yelled for him to show his hands - and when he did, the officer mistook his wallet for a weapon.</description></item><item><title>Ellen Drew</title><link>/ypzuk5p.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ypzuk5p.html</guid><description>Ellen Drew estimated Net Worth, Biography, Age, Height, Dating, Relationship Records, Salary, Income, Cars, Lifestyles &amp;amp; many more details have been updated below. Let’s check, How Rich is Ellen Drew in 2019-2020? Scroll below and check more details information about Current Net worth as well as Monthly/Year Salary, Expense, Income Reports!BiographyEllen Drew was born in Kansas City, MO on November 23, 1915. Popular 1930’s and ’40s actress who became famous for staring in films like Christmas in July in 1940 and Johnny O’Clock in 1947.</description></item><item><title>Natalie Merchant Biography</title><link>/80m5u70.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/80m5u70.html</guid><description>Natalie Anne Merchant is an American singer, musician, and songwriter. She has once been involved with an alternative rock band 10,000 Maniacs in 1981. However, she later, left it to begin her solo musical career.
As of now, Natalie Merchant is in her late-50s. The American singer Natalie has a net worth of $11 Million.&amp;nbsp;
Age &amp;amp; Parents of Natalie Merchant&amp;nbsp;Natalie Merchant was born on born October 26, 1963, in New York City, United States to father Anthony Merchant and mother Ann Merchant in Jamestown, New York.</description></item><item><title>Were all willing Gail to get better Ive told her to put a picture of our daughter on her</title><link>/x5m8yr8.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/x5m8yr8.html</guid><description>JUST days before she checked into rehab, Gail Porter agreed to meet her ex-husband Dan Hipgrave and his new wife Lynsey for a picnic on London’s Hampstead Heath.
To anyone passing on that summer’s day, it must have seemed the typical extended family get-together.
For also with them as they munched sandwiches and enjoyed the sunshine was the former couple’s adorable nine-year-old daughter, Honey.
But the happy scene masked years of torment that have blighted Gail’s life and threatened to separate her from the little girl she treasures.</description></item><item><title>Why Did Sami Gayle Quit Nicky Reagan Part</title><link>/5qckspf.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/5qckspf.html</guid><description>Longtime fans of the CBS multi-generational cop drama, Blue Bloods, have had the chance to watch the Reagan family’s Sunday dinners for over 10 years now. Among the youngest generation of the family in attendance is Nicky Reagan-Boyle, played by Sami Gayle. She has been on the show since its start in 2010 when she was just 14 years old.
Last season, fans of the character were heartbroken when Nicky announced she’d be moving to San Francisco to pursue her career and would no longer be a regular at Sunday dinners.</description></item><item><title>Yvonne Boismier Phillips</title><link>/0zarr8r.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/0zarr8r.html</guid><description>Yvonne Boismier Phillips estimated Net Worth, Biography, Age, Height, Dating, Relationship Records, Salary, Income, Cars, Lifestyles &amp;amp; many more details have been updated below. Let’s check, How Rich is Yvonne Boismier Phillips in 2020-2021? Scroll below and check more detailed information about Current Net worth as well as Monthly/Year salaries, Expenses, Income Reports! Who is Yvonne Boismier Phillips?&amp;nbsp; Yvonne Boismier Phillips is an actor and makeup artist. Phillips is best known for being the better half of Lou Diamond Phillips, an American director.</description></item><item><title>Shaun White Net Worth | Girlfriend</title><link>/u9h02oh.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/u9h02oh.html</guid><description>Shaun White Net Worth – $70 million What is Shaun White’s net worth? Who is Shaun White’s girlfriend?
Introduction Shaun White, known as the Flying Tomato because of his red hair, is an American former professional snowboarder and skateboarder who is the only athlete to score a perfect 100 in superpipe at the 2012 X Games in Aspen.
Biography He was born on September 3, 1986, in San Diego, California, USA, as Shaun Roger White.</description></item><item><title>Is Alex Bregman Gay? More On His Ethnicity and Sexuality -Is He Jewish?</title><link>/qg9ly5m.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/qg9ly5m.html</guid><description>Alex Bregman is currently in the highlight for being featured in the 2021 world series. Find out if the famous Jewish baseball player Alex Bregman is gay or not in this article.&amp;nbsp;
Alex Bregman is undoubtedly the most well-known Jewish baseball player in the league today.
Bregman currently plays for the Major League Baseball’s Houston Astros (MLB). The 27-year-old is a two-time All-Star who placed second in the American League MVP voting in 2019 with 41 home runs and 112 RBI.</description></item><item><title>Christine Minihane Bio, Net Worth, Married, Husband &amp;amp; Children</title><link>/by8dehx.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/by8dehx.html</guid><description>Christine Minihane is best known as the wife of the American radio jockey, Kirk Minihane. Despite being a wife of a star, she keeps her personal life low-key. As per her husband, he is an American radio personality and presenter from Massachusetts, best recognized for his work as a fill-in and hosting the show, Kirk &amp;amp; Callahan of Entercom&amp;nbsp;Sports, a WEEI&amp;nbsp; team.
Christine and her husband, Kirk walked down the aisle after dating for several years.</description></item><item><title>Amy Reimann's Husband and Net Worth [2023 Update]</title><link>/c66xjdq.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/c66xjdq.html</guid><description>Amy Reimann is the famous wife of Ralph Dale Earnhardt Jr., also known as “Dale Jr.” or simply “Junior,” an American professional stock car racing driver.
Reimann is an interior designer by profession and a doting mother of two daughters.
While studying at the University of Kentucky, she was a cheerleader for the Wildcat Dancers.
Aside from her relationship, many people are eager to know about her life. Here we provide details on her personal life, early life, education, etc.</description></item><item><title>'Sweet Home Alabama' Cast: Where Are They Now?</title><link>/zns9o88.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/zns9o88.html</guid><description>Sweet Home Alabama became a classic rom-com almost as soon as it hit theaters in 2002, thanks to the charm — and chemistry — of leads Reese Witherspoon and Josh Lucas.
Witherspoon stars as Melanie Smooter, a New York City fashion designer who hides her Pigeon Creek, Alabama, origins by using the last name “Carmichael.” After getting engaged to Andrew Hennings (Patrick Dempsey) — the son of New York City mayor Kate Hennings (Candice Bergen) — Melanie discovers she’s still married to her childhood sweetheart, Jake Perry (Lucas), as he never signed their divorce papers.</description></item><item><title>Who is Maggio Cipriani dating? Maggio Cipriani girlfriend, wife</title><link>/rfayga1.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rfayga1.html</guid><description>Maggio Cipriani&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Italian Business
01
Whois hedating right now?
According to our records, Maggio Cipriani is possibly single. RelationshipsMaggio Cipriani has been in a relationship with Cheyenne Tozzi (2010 - 2011).
Maggio Cipriani has had an encounter with Lindsay Lohan (2013).
AboutMaggio Cipriani is a 34 year old Italian Business Professional. Born on 5th May, 1989 in Italy, he is famous for Cipriani's Restaurant Empire Heir. His zodiac sign is Taurus.</description></item><item><title>Who Is Rikkie Valerie Kolle? 5 Things On Trans Miss Netherlands Winner Hollywood Life</title><link>/kfgljru.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/kfgljru.html</guid><description>Rikkie Valerie Kolle&amp;nbsp;made history as the first transwoman to win the Miss Netherlands title in the 2023 competition on Sunday, July 9. The model, 22, looked beautiful and overjoyed as she won the title in a long, red dress. In a post celebrating the win, Rikkie shared that she was very excited to represent the country. “I’m so proud and happy I can’t even describe it. Making my community proud and showing it can be done,” she wrote, while thanking the judges and her fellow pageant contestants.</description></item><item><title>Dan Walker's very rare PDA with private wife in romantic oceanside holiday photo</title><link>/48bdk6g.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/48bdk6g.html</guid><description>Former BBC Breakfast star Dan Walker admitted his work commitments caused him to cancel a family holiday earlier this year, but he made it up to his wife by whisking her away to Portugal this week.&amp;nbsp;
The TV presenter rarely shares photos of Sarah and their kids Susanna, Jessica and Joe on social media, but he made an exception to share a peek inside his joyful holiday. As part of a slideshow of photos, Dan shared a snap of himself with his arm wrapped around his wife as they stood on oceanside rocks and looked out to sea.</description></item><item><title>Merrick Hanna</title><link>/yvbu0bx.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/yvbu0bx.html</guid><description>Merrick Hanna estimated Net Worth, Biography, Age, Height, Dating, Relationship Records, Salary, Income, Cars, Lifestyles &amp;amp; many more details have been updated below. Let’s check, How Rich is Merrick Hanna in 2019-2020? Scroll below and check more detailed information about Current Net worth as well as Monthly/Year Salary, Expense, Income Reports!BiographyMerrick Hanna was born in San Diego, CA on March 22, 2005. Freestyle dancer is known for his “flo-bot” style of dance.</description></item><item><title>Pamela Silva Conde</title><link>/m9kfu83.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/m9kfu83.html</guid><description>Pamela Silva Conde estimated Net Worth, Biography, Age, Height, Dating, Relationship Records, Salary, Income, Cars, Lifestyles &amp;amp; many more details have been updated below. Let’s check, How Rich is Pamela Silva Conde in 2019-2020? Scroll below and check more details information about Current Net worth as well as Monthly/Year Salary, Expense, Income Reports! Biography Pamela Silva Conde was born in Lima, Peru on August 16, 1981. Emmy-winning Peruvian journalist and co-anchor of Primer Impacto.</description></item></channel></rss>