<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Trend on PicoVibe</title><link>/categories/trend/</link><description>Recent content in Trend on PicoVibe</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/trend/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How a Local Arizona Newspaper Covered Sacha Baron Cohens Mosque Prank</title><link>/idww3e6.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/idww3e6.html</guid><description>Sacha Baron Cohen on Who Is America? When Sacha Baron Cohen went to Kingman, Arizona, to film a prank for Who Is America? episode two, he got exactly what he wanted. After his liberal character, Dr. Nira Cain-N’Degeocello, led a focus group about plans to replace a local shopping center with a $385 million mosque funded by the Saudi government and the Clinton Foundation — plans that, to put it lightly, did not go over well with the attendees — the event received coverage in a local newspaper, well before Baron Cohen’s prank victims knew who they were dealing with.</description></item><item><title>Kyle Massey Girlfriend, Parents, Net Worth, Now</title><link>/z0lg746.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/z0lg746.html</guid><description>EntertainmentBy Rushali Kapali | On: May 25, 2022Kyle Massey may not require an introduction to Wizard of Oz enthusiasts. For those who are unfamiliar with Kyle, he is an American actor, rapper, and singer. During his tenure in show business, he has worked in both the music and acting areas.
Since his portrayal as Cory Baxter on Disney's That's So Raven, he has been in a number of films, including Life is Ruff, Gotham, Being Mary Jane, and others.</description></item><item><title> Jeffrey Epstein's Gruesome Autopsy Photos, More Suicide Questions Rai</title><link>/j1ihqru.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/j1ihqru.html</guid><description>Gallery Launch Gallery THE GRAPHIC SCENE Launch Gallery Gallery CBS/ 60 Minutes Jeffrey Epstein's autopsy has revealed how he may have killed himself in his jail cell, as photos show nooses fashioned from orange bedsheets ... and the bloody neck wound from where he hanged himself ... but some experts think it could have been murder.
The photographs were obtained by "60 Minutes" and shown Sunday night during an interview about Epstein's apparent suicide and the conspiracy theories that have followed.</description></item><item><title>Savannah Chrisley Frantic on 911 Call as She and Todd Try to Help Suicidal Ex BF</title><link>/w4289l3.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/w4289l3.html</guid><description>subscribe Yes! Send me email updates and offers from TMZ and its Affiliates. By subscribing, I agree to the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use
follow ncG1vNJzZmivp6x7tbnZZ5qopV%2BsrrWvx2hpaWpiYn1zeY9rZGlqYGd%2Fc3nSmq2app6WtW6vx6ugrKSVrnp6fZBmaGxtZGWDdXs%3D</description></item><item><title>Who Is Amybeth McNulty? 5 Things About The New Stranger Things Star Hollywood Life</title><link>/9t8q68f.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/9t8q68f.html</guid><description>There are more new faces joining the cast of Stranger Things. Netflix fan fave Amybeth McNulty was revealed as a new season 4 cast member on June 9. Stranger Things creators Matt and Ross Duffer helped announced Amybeth’s role in a behind-the-scenes video.
Amybeth is no stranger to the Netflix world. The 19-year-old is one of the most talented young actresses out there. From scoop on her Stranger Things character to her personal life, HollywoodLife has 5 key things to know about Amybeth.</description></item><item><title>Is Dr Doug Weiss Divorced? Check About His Marital Status</title><link>/sc4lo5k.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sc4lo5k.html</guid><description>Is Dr Doug Weiss divorced? Take a look at this article to know whether Dr Doug Weiss is divorced and get more infromation about his personal life. Is Dr Doug Weiss Divorced?It is not known if he is divorced or not. Dr. Doug Weiss is a renowned expert in the field of partner betrayal trauma and addiction recovery. With over three decades of experience as a licensed therapist and counselor, he has dedicated his career to helping individuals heal from the devastating effects of betrayal and addiction.</description></item><item><title>Why are only women described as confessional singer-songwriters?</title><link>/rq7hb34.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rq7hb34.html</guid><description>The term has followed Mitchell through her career – much to her annoyance. Photograph: GAB Archive/RedfernsThe term has followed Mitchell through her career – much to her annoyance. Photograph: GAB Archive/RedfernsMusicThe term is loaded with notions of guilt and remorse – and it is rarely ever used about men
With every hour that Joni Mitchell spent in intensive care earlier this month, and with every hour her fans held their breath, braced for the worst, another (premature) tribute made its way online.</description></item><item><title>Nihachu</title><link>/9pwky6f.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/9pwky6f.html</guid><description>Nihachu estimated Net Worth, Biography, Age, Height, Dating, Relationship Records, Salary, Income, Cars, Lifestyles &amp;amp; many more details have been updated below. Let’s check, How Rich is Nihachu in 2020-2021? Scroll below and check more detailed information about Current Net worth as well as Monthly/Year salaries, Expenses, Income Reports!Who is Nihachu?&amp;nbsp;Nihachu, a Twitch broadcaster, YouTuber, and social media influencer from Germany, is well-known. She’s recognized for her podcast-styled broadcasts on a variety of themes, and she’s also streamed games like Minecraft, The Sims 4, and Stardew Valley.</description></item><item><title>'The Gilded Age' Casting News Hints at What's in Store for Season 2</title><link>/xp2sc8t.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/xp2sc8t.html</guid><description>TL;DR: The Gilded Age Season 2 will feature expanded roles for several below-stairs characters. New cast members for the HBO series include Michael Braugher as Booker T. Washington and Ben Lamb as the Duke of Buckingham. Thomas Cocquerel will not return as Tom Raikes. HBO’s The Gilded Age is returning for season 2 – and expanding its cast in the process. The period drama from creator Julian Fellowes will add new characters in its sophomore outing while also upping a number of season 1 cast members to series regulars.</description></item></channel></rss>