<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>News on PicoVibe</title><link>/categories/news/</link><description>Recent content in News on PicoVibe</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Demi Rose Mawbyspills the secrets on expanding derriere</title><link>/lg3xwq2.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/lg3xwq2.html</guid><description>Her 6.2 million Instagram followers regularly marvel at her eye-popping curves.
And Demi Rose Mawby has offered her fans a chance to nab a bottom as bountiful as hers, as she revealed toThe Sun her highly sought after body secrets.&amp;nbsp;
The social media star, 22, whose derriere has noticeably increased over the years, admitted that 'genes, a hell of a lot of hard work and dedication in the gym and a good well balanced nutritious diet' is all that is needed to achieve similar results.</description></item><item><title>Dax Shepard Will Punch Everyone in Hollywood in the Face</title><link>/nnqtm6a.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/nnqtm6a.html</guid><description>Dax Shepard’s Brother’s Justice is a mockumentary about Shepard trying to reinvent himself as a martial arts expert, despite no training or expertise at all. It looks pretty entertaining! It just premiered at the Austin Film Festival last week and is currently being shopped around to distributors.
Dax Shepard Will Punch Everyone in Hollywood in the […] ncG1vNJzZmivp6x7t8HLrayrnV6YvK57kWloaWdhZXylrddmqqGdoJ2us7CMsKClpF2lwq%2Bvx2acr52irryvsYyipWagn6G5usPOqJtmoZ5iwamxjJ%2BYnJ1encGuuA%3D%3D</description></item><item><title>Jon Ronson on the fall of Alex Jones: Politics Weekly America | Politics</title><link>/iev620m.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/iev620m.html</guid><description>Politics Weekly America US politics Jon Ronson on the fall of Alex Jones: Politics Weekly America More ways to listen Apple Podcasts Google Podcasts Spotify RSS Feed Download Presented by Jonathan Freedland, with Jon Ronson, produced by Danielle Stephens and executive producer Nicole Jackson.
Fri 29 Apr 2022 05.00&amp;nbsp;BST Last modified on Tue 31 May 2022 12.</description></item><item><title> Cops: Ne-Yo Was Driving CRAZY!</title><link>/2wj06b0.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2wj06b0.html</guid><description>TMZ has learned that R&amp;amp;B singer Ne-Yo, aka Shaffer Smith, was popped on Feb. 19 while driving through Cobb County, Georgia. That's so sick!
Cops pulled Ne-Yo after they observed him driving well over 100 mph in his 2006 Range Rover. He was arrested for reckless driving and for not having a valid license.
Maybe he was rushing to the Hair Club for Men. WTF's up with that receding hairline?</description></item><item><title>What Do the Rockettes Do for the Rest of the Year? Details</title><link>/25bp0lj.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/25bp0lj.html</guid><description>The Radio City Rockettes are a staple during the holiday season, but what do they do for the rest of the year? Discover their off-season work.
When we think of New York City during the holiday season, the seasonal Christmas Spectular Starring the Radio City Rockettes immediately comes to mind. Founded in 1925, the Rockettes quickly transitioned from St. Louis to Radio City in New York, where they've been performing since 1932.</description></item><item><title>Estelle Cruijff (TV Actress) - Age, Birthday, Bio, Facts, Family, Net Worth, Height &amp;amp; More</title><link>/utu7rs3.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/utu7rs3.html</guid><description>TV Actress Estelle Cruijff was born in Amsterdam, Netherlands on June 29, 1978. She's 45 years old today.
In 2017, she was a TV actress and reality personality who competed in and won The Perfect Picture.
All info about Estelle Cruijff can be found here. This article will clarify all information about Estelle Cruijff: biography, net worth, career, talent, spouse and breakup...
Estelle Cruijff was born in the Zodiac sign Cancer (The Crab), and 1978 is the year of the Chinese Zodiac Horse (馬).</description></item><item><title>Tattoo You: The New Needle of Hip Hop</title><link>/iisswa1.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/iisswa1.html</guid><description>As anybody who follows mainstream Rap and the people who create the leading soundtrack for our Hip Hop culture can confirm, a unique sense of fashion is just as important to the rhyme-sayer as his or her flow. While having the latest footwear and clothing is a plus, many entertainers have found a more personal way of establishing their brand among fans.
Hence the accessory of choice for many an emcee: the tattoo.</description></item><item><title>Out with the Old, In with the New</title><link>/34kmtfo.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/34kmtfo.html</guid><description>Elisabeth Röhm, best known for her roles as Serena on Law &amp;amp; Order and Kate on Angel, is marking a year blogging for PEOPLE.com. The actress will appear on CSI: Miami this Sunday, Jan. 29. She also has a role on The Client List and upcoming films Transit and Officer Down out later this year. She can be found on Facebook, Google + and @ElisabethRohm. In her latest blog, Röhm — mom to 3½-year-old Easton August with Ron Anthony — gets a 2012 wake up call when her fiancé suggests her resolution includes chucking the mom clothes!</description></item><item><title>5 TV Shows Like 90 Day Fiance That You Can Watch Now</title><link>/r0yq2ob.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/r0yq2ob.html</guid><description>Reality TV shows are a great escape from the mundane lives we have. These shows provide a way of entertaining us, whether through romance, adventure, or anything else.
Among the many fantastic reality shows on offer today, the ones that put romantic relationships on the stake are the most exciting to watch. And on that front, 90 Day Fiancé is the gold standard to beat.
90 Day Fiancé showcases international couples that arrive on US soil to decide their lives in front of the cameras.</description></item><item><title>Majo Aguilar Parents: Who Are Her Parents? Singer Net Worth &amp;amp; Wiki</title><link>/kqtjn3o.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/kqtjn3o.html</guid><description>Majo is a member of the Aguilar clan, also referred to as the singing clan. The entire family is an accomplished singer. Mexican singer and composer Majo Aguilar performs for Universal Music Group.
Aguliar started performing professionally in 2016, but she had previously started streaming her music and recording an album with her family. She originally released Triste Recuerdo, her first music video, in 2016. After then, Aguliar continues to post cover songs and videos of her original music on YouTube.</description></item><item><title>Alpharad (Youtuber) Wiki, Biography, Age, Height, Weight, Wife, Net Worth, Facts</title><link>/utakc4o.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/utakc4o.html</guid><description>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
John Jacob Rabon IV, an American influencer on Youtuber and social media, is the real name of Alpharad. He is well known for his channel on YouTube, where games such as Zelda’s Legend and Sonic are played. In series such as How to Play 101, Tale For Glory, and Challenge Mode, he even increased to popularity. There were more than 2.2 million viewers attracted to his AlpharadTV channel.</description></item><item><title>Sasha Roiz Married, Wife, Gay, Height, Body Measurements, Bio</title><link>/f37cuz4.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/f37cuz4.html</guid><description>Sasha Roiz is an Israeli-Canadian actress. He is best known for his role as Captain Sean Renard in the fantastic television series Grimm which was created in October 2011 and ended in March 2017. The end of the series was sad news for most fans who simply hadn’t finished seeing more of their favorite stars in action.
Roiz is also known for films such as Unthinkable (2010) Extracted (2012) and Pompeii (2014).</description></item><item><title>Do Jenner sisters Kylie and Kendall participate in the Kardashian Christmas card?</title><link>/jvtfn6z.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/jvtfn6z.html</guid><description>THE KARDASHIAN Christmas card is a highly-anticipated set of photos released annually, typically on Christmas Eve.
For the 2021 card, only Kim and Khloe Kardashian appeared alongside their mother Kris Jenner and most of her grandchildren. Do Jenner sisters Kylie and Kendall participate in the Kardashian Christmas card? Kylie and Kendall Jenner are Kris' youngest daughters, born from her relationship with former Olympian Caitlyn Jenner.
Although they are half-sisters to the Kardashian trio and Rob, the two often appear in the annual Kardashian Christmas card.</description></item><item><title>Donnell Whittenburg's mysterious Dating life, know about his Affairs, Relationship, and Career</title><link>/bl2zl6w.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/bl2zl6w.html</guid><description>Donnell Whittenburg; is he Married? Know about his Affairs and Relationship including his Career and Net Worth An American artistic gymnast Donnell Whittenburg is rising as one of the best gymnasts in after winning a bronze medal in 2014's World Artistic Gymnastics Championships.
The 23-year-old gymnast after being entitled as 2014's U.S. National Champion on the Vault and as the 2015 U.S. National Champion on the Rings, becoming a hot topic among the ladies and we all want to know whether he 's dating someone or he's already married?</description></item><item><title>Jessica Biel Ethnicity, Nationality, Race, Family, Body measurements, career</title><link>/eup5xlr.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/eup5xlr.html</guid><description>Jessica Biel is a well-known actress, model, and producer in Hollywood. She has been in the industry for over two decades and has starred in numerous movies and TV shows. However, not many people know about her ethnic background and personal life. In this article, we will explore Jessica Biel’s ethnicity, family background, personal life, and career.
Ethnicity, Ethnic Background, Nationality, and Race: Jessica Biel is of mixed ethnicity.</description></item></channel></rss>